Bonus Short Stories

You Pervert!

Rio had finished his chores for the day in the stone house and was taking a breather on the sofa in the living room. Draped in his favorite blanket, he felt a light drowsiness overcome him and napped for half an hour or so.

“Hmm...?”

At some point in time, Aishia and Latifa had sat down on either side of him and fallen asleep against his shoulders. It was just the three of them in the living room.

...I can’t get up at this rate.

Seeing the two of them sleeping so soundly made him reluctant to stand up and wake them. But at the same time, they’d have cricks in their necks if they continued to sleep like this.

Maybe I should carry them to bed instead? Rio pondered.

“Oh, you’re awake, Rio,” Celia said, walking in along with Sara.

“Yes. Where has everyone else gone?” Rio asked, looking around the living room.

“We were just having tea in Orphia’s room, but we ran out of snacks, so we came out to restock,” Sara replied with a giggle.

“I see. While you’re here, could you take this blanket off of me? I can’t seem to move right now.”

“Sure, hold on.” At Rio’s request, Celia approached to take the blanket off him.

“...Mm. Morning.” Aishia slowly blinked her eyes open.

“Morning, Aishia. Still sleepy?” Rio asked, watching Aishia rub her eyes.

“Yeah...” Aishia nodded, still half asleep.

“Can you change into your spirit form and enter me for a moment? I’m going to carry Latifa to bed.”

“All right.” Aishia immediately disappeared. With that, Rio was free to move.

“Okay. I’m going to take Latifa to bed, then.” He turned to her and lifted her up in his arms in a familiar manner. Latifa’s mouth relaxed into a happy smile as she entrusted herself to Rio.

“She sleeps so happily.” Celia watched Latifa’s sleeping face and smiled.

“She sometimes feigns it, though,” Sara said with a sigh.

“She is a fox werebeast, after all,” Celia laughed in amusement.

“I’ll be going, then,” Rio said, and started walking towards Latifa’s room. Meanwhile, Sara went to grab snacks from the kitchen and headed back to Orphia’s room with Celia. Orphia and Alma were waiting inside.

“Welcome back, you two,” Orphia called out to the two of them with a warm smile.

“...What’s with the blanket?” Alma asked, seeing Celia.

“Ah, it’s Rio’s...”

The blanket was still warm from Rio’s body heat; she had folded it while Sara had gone to get the snacks. Rio hadn’t returned, so she ended up carrying it with her—almost as though she couldn’t bear to part with it. Sara, Orphia, and Alma’s gazes naturally gathered on the blanket.

“Now that I think about it, there was no need to bring it with me. Rio might be back already, so I should go leave it in the living room,” Celia said with a high pitch to her voice. She felt embarrassed for some reason.

“Hehe, why don’t you take the opportunity to try sleeping with Rio’s blanket? It’s still warm, right? I’m sure it’d feel wonderful,” Orphia said to Celia with a mischievous smile.

Celia blinked a few times before blushing red. “Huh? I-I can’t do that!”

“Then how about you, Sara? Alma?” Orphia asked the two of them.

“W-What are you saying, Orphia?” Sara asked bashfully, seemingly shaken by that. Alma pretended that she hadn’t heard to avoid digging her own grave.

“Really? Then I’ll borrow it and sleep with it,” Orphia giggled, looking at Celia.

“Y-You can’t do that! Pervert!” Celia hugged the blanket to herself tightly.

“Hehe, it was just a joke,” Orphia said in amusement.

“...Geez.” Celia’s cheeks remained scarlet as she pouted.

“Orphia looks serious, but she can be quite the prankster,” Sara sighed tiredly.

The longer she held onto it, the more likely the conversation would take a strange turn. That thought made Celia stand up. “Ahaha... I’m going to leave the blanket in the living room. Rio might be back by now.”

“Too bad for you, Sara.”

“It’s not like that!”

Leaving the bickering girls behind her, Celia returned to the living room alone.

“Rio’s still not here...”

No one was in the living room. Celia headed towards the sofa Rio had been sleeping on earlier. She was about to place it down on the sofa, when—

“...Hmph.”

The warmth of the blanket was so comforting, she hesitated to let go. Celia stared at it. After several seconds, she suddenly hugged it close and buried her face in the blanket.

“...Warm.”

And it also smelled like Rio, probably. Sara and Latifa would know for sure...

Wait, what am I doing?! Stop! Now I’m the pervert!

Celia snapped out of it and hurriedly brought the blanket away from her face. But even then, she couldn’t help yearn for that warmth, feeling envious of Aishia and Latifa, who always clung to Rio without reserve.

“O-One more time, just one...”

Celia gently brought the blanket close to her face again. But when the door to Latifa’s room opened with a clack! she flinched upright and froze.

“...Huh? Professor? You’re still here.”

Rio cocked his head curiously at Celia standing alone in the living room. Thankfully, he hadn’t seen any of what Celia had herself dubbed perverted.

Celia exhaled in relief and controlled her thumping heart as much as she could to give a calm answer. “Y-Yeah. I accidentally took your blanket to Orphia’s room, so I was bringing it back.”

One Scene of the Banquet

On the first night of the banquet hosted by the Kingdom of Galarc, when Satsuki was first introduced, Miharu stood beside Rio with Liselotte, the three of them moving together.

There was a constant stream of nobility coming to greet them, so they had yet to move since the beginning of the banquet, receiving one noble after another on the upper floor.

The main guest of the night was the hero, Satsuki, so she had been gathering the most attention, but Miharu had gathered nearly as much attention from the nobles. While part of the reason was because she was Satsuki’s friend, her elegant beauty also played a large part.

“Goodness me, what a wonderful sight. That black hair on such a maiden...”

“Indeed. Both Lady Satsuki’s radiance and Lady Miharu’s elegance—there must be plenty of young men falling for them.”

The middle-aged nobles with families praised Miharu in awe. Many of the nobles had fallen for her exotic beauty, which was rarely seen in the Strahl region, and were staring at her with heated gazes. But at the same time, Rio was garnering envy for being waited upon by both Miharu and Liselotte, one of the most beautiful bachelorettes of the Galarc Kingdom.

The gazes I can feel... are probably not just my imagination.

Rio could guess the reason behind most of those gazes and mustered a pained smile. Liselotte must have noticed, too, but she was used to such situations and looked perfectly calm. Meanwhile, Miharu hadn’t seemed to notice the heated gazes yet.

“What’s the matter, Haruto?” Miharu immediately noticed Rio looking at her and spoke up. He was a little surprised at how aware Miharu had been of his gaze, but smiled anyway.

“It’s nothing. Are you tired?”

“I’m fine,” Miharu replied with a grin. Seeing her smile from close-up made an indescribable emotion swell within Rio. Whether it was Amakawa Haruto or Rio’s, he didn’t know.

“That’s good to hear,” Rio replied with a smile, hiding the feelings residing in his heart.

Magic Words to Make Omurice Taste Better

Not long before Miharu was to attend the banquet at the Galarc Kingdom, Rio had left the stone house on his own, so Miharu, Latifa, and Celia prepared lunch a little later than usual. Once he returned, Rio waited in the dining room for them to finish cooking.

“Thanks for waiting, Onii-chan!”

Latifa appeared with a tray, accompanied by Miharu and Celia.

“Ta-da! Onii-chan’s favorite—omurice! Miharu taught Celia and I how to make it in a delicious way! What do you think?” Latifa showed off the omurice on the tray with a carefree smile.

“Thank you—it looks delicious. And thanks to Miharu and Professor Celia too.”

“I-It was nothing. I was just a little curious about how it was made after hearing omurice was your favorite and finding it delicious when I tried it. I didn’t do anything in particular,” Celia replied shyly to Rio’s gratitude.

“That’s not true. Celia made most of the chicken rice.” Miharu added with a giggle.

“Hey hey, Onii-chan. Can I put ketchup on top of your omurice?” Latifa asked, eyes sparkling.

“Yeah, sure.” Rio nodded easily. Latifa proceeded to write “I love you” in ketchup over the soft, half-cooked egg.

“Done. It’s filled with our love, so make sure you eat it all up!” Latifa grinned, looking into Rio’s face. Celia and Miharu both looked embarrassed at her words.

“Got it,” Rio replied awkwardly. He picked up the spoon to hide his embarrassment.

“Ah, wait! This isn’t finished yet,” Latifa called out.

“...Huh? Really? Didn’t Miharu just say it was complete?” Celia cocked her head, looking at Miharu.

“Yes. Because we still haven’t said the magic words to make it taste even better,” Latifa huffed proudly and puffed up her modest, still-developing chest.

“Magic words...?” As a sorcerer, Celia’s eyes widened in interest.

“Hehehe! I’m going to say them now, before it gets cold.” Latifa grinned mischievously.

“Make it delicious, ruff ruff kyun!”

Her fox ears twitched as she used both hands to make a heart shape and poured her love into the omurice.

“W-What... is that...?” Celia asked, her face a deep red.

“They’re magic words to add love to the omurice. Now it’s your turn, you two! Let’s see...”

Latifa brought her face up to Celia and Miharu’s ears, whispering something into them. She was probably teaching them the magic words.

“N-No way! I can’t say something that embarrassing!” Celia was taken aback, still flushed red. Miharu tried to smile to cover her shyness.

“I-It’s a little too much for me too...”

“Hmph, I can’t believe you two won’t give Onii-chan their love.” Latifa pouted a little.

“I-I didn’t say that!” Celia objected in a fluster.

“Really? Then let’s see you do what I taught you, Celia.”

“Ugh...”

“Professor, there’s no need to force yourself to do it.” Rio tried to offer a lifeline to Celia, who had effectively dug her own grave.

“I... I’m not forcing myself. M-Make it delicious, lovey-dovey kyun.”

With a bright red face and whisper of a voice, Celia made a heart shape with her hands. But she soon reached the limit of embarrassment she could take and buried her face in her hands with a groan.

Latifa excitedly turned to Miharu. “Now it’s your turn!”

“Umm...” Miharu was doused in anxiety, her voice more high-pitched than usual.

“That’s enough. You’re upsetting Miharu, so just leave it at that. Miharu, you don’t have to go along with her,” Rio sighed tiredly, then picked up the spoon to begin to eat.

“Ah, w-wait a minute!” Miharu called out to stop Rio.

“I-I’d feel bad for Celia if I-I was the only one who didn’t do it... So... M-Make it delicious, moe moe, kyun... Wah.” Miharu mumbled, making a heart with her hands.

Elemental ☆ Admission

In Japan, somewhere in the city...

It was springtime, and pale pink petals danced in the wind during the entrance ceremony for schools. Haruto was visiting the campus of the parent university of his affiliated school.

He wasn’t there because he was starting his tenure at university, but he was there to celebrate his upperclassman’s entrance.

“Congratulations, Satsuki.”

On the afternoon of the entrance ceremony, he waited a little earlier than their meetup time to offer words of congratulations to Satsuki, who arrived later.

“Thank you, Haruto. What do you think of my hakama? Does it suit me?” Satsuki giggled, lifting her arms lightly to show off her hakama.

“Yes, it’s beautiful. Both the hakama and you in it,” Haruto praised with a wide smile.

Satsuki’s cheeks reddened with embarrassment, before she turned her slightly reproachful eyes to Haruto. “...You sure don’t have any hesitation saying things like that. And yet, it doesn’t sound smug or fake at all.”

“Umm, did I say something wrong?” Haruto asked awkwardly at Satsuki’s gaze.

“Nope, you were completely on point. Thanks.” Satsuki sighed lightly but thanked him happily anyway.

“But if you say that to every girl, you may make some people misunderstand your intent, so make sure you choose who you say it to even if it’s just flattery,” she pointed a finger at Haruto and added.

“It wasn’t flattery. And I said it because it’s you, Satsuki.”

“...” Satsuki blinked for a few moments before turning her face diagonally away from Haruto.

“I really will misunderstand, stupid,” she muttered so that Haruto couldn’t hear.

“...Satsuki?” Haruto called out to her, wondering what was wrong.

“It’s nothing, I’m just fed up with your inability to learn. Are Miharu and the others still on their way here?” Satsuki stated bluntly, looking around at their surroundings.

“Y-Yeah. There’s still a little while before the meetup time.” Haruto winced a little, glancing at the public clock nearby.

“Hmm. I guess we’re on our own until then,” Satsuki said casually.

“So it seems,” Haruto replied normally.

Satsuki pouted a little before she suddenly watched the people passing by and turned to Haruto. “...By the way, does it feel like we’re being stared at?” They were currently within the university campus, on the grounds right next to the affiliated school Haruto attended. Because of that, there were fewer people visiting for the entrance ceremony, but there were still bustling groups here and there.

“Isn’t it because of you, Satsuki?”

“Me?”

“Because you’re beautiful in your hakama,” said Haruto.

“...T-That’s not true!” Satsuki was clearly embarrassed, but she must have been discontent with being the only one feeling embarrassed. “There aren’t many chances to be alone with a girl in a hakama. Good for you, right Haruto?” she asked him with a glare.

“Yes, indeed,” Haruto agreed with an amused chuckle.

“...For some reason, I just want to see you looking embarrassed, even if it’s the last thing I do.” Satsuki puffed up her cheeks and stared at Haruto.

“Why? Please, don’t.”

“Take that!” Satsuki cheekily hugged Haruto’s arm as he backed away warily. They were the spitting image of lovers, making the male students passing by glare at them with envy.

“Wha—Satsuki?!” Haruto finally felt embarrassed and blushed.

“It’s rare to be hugged by a girl in a hakama, so isn’t this great? If you want, I’ll even wear it again—just for you,” Satsuki said, looking at Haruto with a carefree smile.

Chapter 4: A Family Reunion

The next day, Rio followed the plan they had arranged the night before and received permission to leave the castle in the morning. Aishia and the other girls had brought Aki and Masato to the capital already, but they couldn’t go to the castle quite yet.

The purpose of Rio’s outing was to create a cover story for King Francois, to prove that he had met with Aki and Masato to confirm their intentions. They couldn’t possibly give him the explanation that they had snuck out of the castle at night to meet in secret already, after all. Rio spent two hours outside of the castle before returning to finally set things in motion with Satsuki and Miharu.

After requesting an audience with King Francois in one of the castle’s drawing rooms, they told him there were people they wanted to invite to the castle. Takahisa and Lilianna were also summoned to the room, and Michel and Charlotte were present as well. Satsuki took the lead on explaining, being that she was the hero.

She spoke of how Rio had been looking after Aki and Masato together with Miharu, about how they wanted to see Takahisa, and as a result, they wished to summon the two of them to the castle. They weren’t brought to the castle in the first place because the two of them were too young to attend the banquet.

“I understand. You may invite them to the castle immediately. If they are Sir Takahisa’s siblings, then I presume it would be fine for them to lodge in your quarters?” Francois approved once Satsuki had explained everything to a rough degree.

“Yes!” Takahisa nodded eagerly, and so it was decided that Aki and Masato would be brought to the castle. After that, Rio left the castle in the company of an official and headed straight for Aki and Masato. Miharu went with him, after offering to go as well.

They went to the meet-up location they had decided on beforehand and safely brought Aki and Masato back to the castle, then headed straight for the drawing room they’d occupied before.

“Takahisa!” Aki yelled in delight as soon as she entered the room and spotted him. Masato stood right behind her with a shy smile on his face.

“Aki! Masato!” Takahisa jumped out of the chair he was sitting in and ran towards the two of them, overcome with emotion.

“It’s you! I can’t believe it’s you!” Aki dashed forward to hug him. Takahisa opened his arms to catch her.

“Aki! I’m so glad you’re safe, seriously...!” Takahisa squeezed her tightly.

“Ahaha, that hurts,” Aki said, though she was hugging her brother just as strongly.

“Oops, sorry.” Takahisa reflexively tried to loosen his hold.

“Nope, this time it’s my turn. Hehe... it’s really you.” Aki squeezed her arms even tighter. She buried her face in Takahisa’s chest. Even a normally cool-headed girl like her had a childish side.

“How have you been, Aki? I, uhh... heard you were nearly made into a slave...”

“Yup, I’ve been good. Haruto... He saved me,” Aki replied with a shadow over her smile. She almost looked at Rio, but stopped herself partway.

“I see. Well, you’re safe now—I’ll protect you.”

“...Yeah.” Aki nodded vaguely. Seeing her unhappy expression made Takahisa’s face cloud over with frustration. He bit down on his lip and looked at Rio.

“...Umm. Thank you very much, Haruto. For protecting the three of them. Really.”

“Not a problem,” Rio replied shortly, shaking his head.

“How have you been, Masato? Come closer—show me your face,” Takahisa said to Masato, who was standing a distance away.

“I’m fine. Don’t be embarrassing about it,” Masato replied awkwardly.

“You’ve grown so much in our short time apart,” Takahisa said in a brotherly way.

“Really? Well, I’m still growing,” Masato huffed shyly and looked at his own limbs.

“You siblings get along so well. But I really am glad the five of us could reunite like this safely. Long time no see, Aki, Masato.” Satsuki had been watching the family reunion warmly until now, when she decided to address them. Only Rio, Miharu, and the two siblings involved knew that Satsuki had snuck out of the castle to go see them before the banquet, so she needed to pretend she was meeting them again for the first time.

“Long time no see, Satsuki,” Aki said.

“Yeah, it’s good to see you’re safe as well,” Masato chimed in. They gave their replies as they had planned—as though they were meeting again for the first time.

“If you have all been reunited safely, then we shall take our leave. It would be impolite for us to intrude on such a long-awaited reunion,” Francois said, looking at Lilianna.

“Yes. We shall give our proper greetings at a later time,” Lilianna agreed immediately.

“If you don’t mind, Sir Haruto, could you please accompany me?” Charlotte suddenly asked Rio.

“Of course.” With no reason to refuse the request of a princess, Rio nodded readily. Thus, everyone other than the five people from Earth left the room. The door clicked shut, leaving the five of them alone.

“How about we all sit down first? Miharu, you can sit next to me,” Satsuki suggested.

“Right.” Takahisa nodded happily, guiding Aki to the sofa for them to sit together. Masato sat down on a sofa a slight distance away, while Miharu seated herself beside Satsuki.

“I know we’ve finally reunited and are in high spirits, but we already have a general idea of each other’s circumstances and it’s quite difficult to find time for the five of us to be together, so how about we discuss the things that need to be said first?” Satsuki said, looking around at everyone’s faces.

“Sure. But what do we need to discuss?” Takahisa looked at Satsuki and cocked his head.

“The serious matter of our future. Everything’s really complicated right now, right? Neither Takahisa nor I can leave our kingdoms easily, and we’ll probably be separated again in the future. Looking at things in the long-term, shouldn’t we decide on what to do in order to return to Earth?” Satsuki said, summarizing the agenda succinctly.

“That’s true...” Takahisa nodded, glancing over at Miharu opposite him.

“There’s something you should know involving Haruto first. It’s heavily related to our future, too. I’ve received permission to tell you about it, but you have to keep what I’m about to say an absolute secret from anyone else. Can you promise me that?” Satsuki looked directly at Takahisa.

“If you’re talking to just me, then the others...” Takahisa looked around.

“They know already. If you can promise me you’ll keep it a secret, then I’ll tell you too. If you can’t make that promise, then I’ll just tell you the conclusion with the detailed explanation omitted, so keep that in mind. Just don’t ask the others to tell you, because they’ve promised already and would be troubled by that.” Satsuki’s explanation was so abstract, there was no way of telling what the matter was about. However, Takahisa didn’t want to be the only one left out of the loop.

“...All right. I promise. Please tell me.”

“Okay. To start with the conclusion... We may not be returning to Earth within the next four years.” Satsuki stated.

“...Four years? How do you know that?” It was a strangely specific number.

“There’s someone who died in Japan four years after we disappeared on our way home—and was reborn into this world. That person heard from your own mother that Miharu was still missing four years later.”

“...What?” What is going on? Takahisa made a dubious face.

“That person is now Haruto, and he used to be Aki’s older brother in his past life. His name was Amakawa Haruto. He was separated from Aki when his parents divorced. Masato wasn’t aware of him, but perhaps you know of this, Takahisa...?” Satsuki asked, but Takahisa’s eyes were completely blank with shock. The words being said were entering his head, but he couldn’t quite accept them as reality so readily.

“Aki, you had an older brother other than me...?” Takahisa turned his head to the side, straining himself to ask Aki.

“I do not. You’re the only brother I have right now. The only one...” Aki furrowed her brow and squeezed Takahisa’s hand.

“As you can see, Aki has feelings of reservation towards Amakawa Haruto. This is just my speculation, but the reason why your parents didn’t tell you two about Haruto’s existence was probably related to that.” Satsuki sighed quietly.

“Aki...” Takahisa squeezed Aki’s hand back to reassure her.

“Amakawa Haruto was also Miharu’s childhood friend. He was separated from her as well when his parents divorced when they were seven years old,” Satsuki continued.

“Miharu’s...?” Takahisa’s eyes widened as his expression stiffened.

“That’s right. Haruto is the reincarnation of my childhood friend.” Miharu verified Satsuki’s statement with a serious expression.

“Uh...” Takahisa paled as his heart throbbed unpleasantly. He didn’t understand why, but he couldn’t help but feel terrified that there was a part of Miharu he didn’t know about.

“Let’s get back to the topic at hand. According to Haruto’s memories, Aki’s mother said that Miharu was still missing. However, she also said that Aki was doing well when asked about her.”

“...Does that mean Aki returns to Earth while Miharu doesn’t?” That was ridiculous. Takahisa couldn’t believe that Aki and Miharu would be separated. He looked dubious.

“Yes. Whether this was a lie to prevent Haruto from worrying or whether it was the truth—and what this could mean if it was the truth—there’s just no way of knowing,” Satsuki said thoughtfully, a troubled shadow over her elegant face.

“...W-Wait a minute! I can’t believe Aki and Miharu would be separated. Was Haruto unaware of the fact that Aki had disappeared? If so, wouldn’t he know that Mom lied when she said Aki was doing well...?!” Takahisa insisted in a heated panic.

“...Haruto was unaware of the fact Aki had gone missing. After his parents divorced, Haruto’s father completely cut off any information about Aki and their mother from reaching him,” Satsuki replied, glancing at Aki for a moment. Aki’s mouth was twisted in a bitter frown at the mention of her father.

“But... I just can’t believe it. There’s no way Aki and Miharu could’ve been separated. Couldn’t Mom have been lying to stop Haruto from worrying?” Takahisa said, this time causing Miharu to be the one to retain a bitter smile.

“...True, that’s another likely possibility. I find it hard to believe that Aki wouldn’t go and find the past Haruto once she returned to Earth, too...” Satsuki looked over at Aki. “At any rate, it doesn’t seem like we’ll be returning to Earth anytime soon. Reluctant as I am to admit, that’s practically been confirmed now. And so, we should have a proper discussion about how we’re going to live in this world from now on, instead of having just a vague idea. Wouldn’t you agree?”

“Yes,” Miharu nodded firmly in approval.

“To be honest, for me... I was pretty panicked until Haruto appeared with Miharu. I was lonely. I had wondered if Miharu and the others were also summoned into this world, but I had no proof, and I just wanted to go home as soon as possible. But you know, I’m more optimistic now. Everyone’s here. I’ve made a very reliable friend in Haruto. So I can’t remain pessimistic about this forever, you know? If we’re not going to be able to return for a while—or even ever—then I want to get a proper footing in this world and live a meaningful life.” Satsuki looked around at everyone as she gave her own thoughts.

“Until now, we’ve only discussed things vaguely. We wondered what we’d do if we met up with Satsuki and Takahisa. We all have our own thoughts on things, but we kind of ended up avoiding that discussion... But I think it’s something that should be discussed properly, now that the five of us have gathered,” Miharu stated her opinion clearly.

“Right. It may be impossible for the five of us to live together, but as long as we know we’re all safe, as long as we know we can see each other again... I think we’d be able to manage.” Satsuki nodded.

“The five of us together, huh... True, with Satsuki as a hero of the Galarc Kingdom, it’d be difficult for her to live in the Centostella Kingdom.” Takahisa looked at Satsuki with a frown.

“Well, yeah...” Satsuki nodded awkwardly.

“...Are you going back to Centostella right away?” Aki tugged at Takahisa’s sleeve and asked.

“Yeah. I’ll probably be able to come out again, but I don’t think I can stay for long. That’s why I thought about what I wanted to do all night. I want everyone to come with me. I want to stay with you all forever. I’ll protect you. I’ll definitely protect you all.” Takahisa’s face was pulled into a tense expression to convey his determination as he looked at Aki, Masato, and finally—Miharu.

“I also want to stay with you...” Despite replying with that, there was a faint touch of hesitation in Aki’s voice. She did want to stay with Takahisa. However, she may have been troubled by whether it was okay to throw aside the bonds she had made living with the others in the stone house up until this point.

“Hmm...” Masato hummed. He seemed to be indecisive and unwilling to answer.

“I’m sorry. I won’t be going to Centostella Kingdom.” Miharu made her refusal loud and clear.

“W-Why...” Takahisa asked hoarsely.

“Because I intend on staying with Haruto...” Miharu replied immediately.

“Wha...” Takahisa made a face as though he had been shoved off a cliff. Speechless, he looked at Miharu imploringly, but she had nothing more to add.

Meanwhile, when Aki heard Miharu’s clear intention to stay with Haruto, her mouth twisted reflexively into a sullen frown.

“I also want to stay with Haruto, I think. I wavered a bit, having you in front of me, but I still want to stay with Haruto for now,” Masato stated.

“But why...” Takahisa was clearly enraged as he mumbled in a quiet voice.

“U-Umm! I want to stay with you!” Aki seemed to have heard Takahisa mumbling from her place beside him, as she hurriedly declared her own position.

“Aki...!” Takahisa’s expression brightened as though he had found an oasis in the desert.

“It’s not that I don’t want to stay with you, bro. It’s just... Haruto’s looked after us so much and I can’t imagine walking away just like ‘Okay, thanks, bye...’ I know you’re ignoring Haruto right now, but you understand how it feels too, right, Aki?” Masato asked her.

“...” Aki seemed unable to be as honest as Masato and held her tongue. However, that was the greatest proof that she felt the same way.

Was Haruto that big of an influence on Masato and Aki? They had only been separated for a few months... Takahisa fell into the illusion that his precious bonds were being stolen and clenched his fists tightly.

Masato sighed at Aki’s lack of a response and voiced his own thoughts once again. “Also, in my case, I have my sword training, too... I don’t want to lose my progress. That’s why I can’t go with you right now, bro. Not until I’ve grown up enough to stand on my own.”

“Sword training?! You— You’re learning how to use a sword?” It was a comment that couldn’t be ignored.

“I am...” Masato was slightly taken aback by Takahisa’s excessive reaction.

“Why are you learning it? It’s not fun and games. Swords are used to kill people in this world.” Since he was learning to use swords at the castle himself, he understood that fact well. Or rather—he was being made to learn it. That was why he showed such an extreme reaction to the knowledge that Masato was learning as well.

“I know. Haruto’s teaching me everything. And if you know that much, that means you’re learning how to master the sword yourself, no?” Masato pointed out how hypocritical that was.

“It’s fine for me to. I’m already in high school, and I understand things. But you’re still in elementary school. Your sense of morals and ethics aren’t developed yet.”

“I understand things, too!”

“D-Don’t tell me you’ve actually killed someone before.” What if he had? Takahisa suddenly paled.

“No way! But there are monsters out there, and the world is what it is. I have to be able to protect us if anything bad ever happens. We were nearly abducted the moment we came to this world, after all,” Masato objected in a rough tone of voice.

“That’s why I’m saying I’ll protect you from now on. You won’t need to set foot anywhere dangerous of your own accord. As long as you stay in the castle, nothing bad will ever happen. It’s safe there.”

“I’m telling you, I’m not going with you! I don’t want to just sit there and be protected.”

“If you fight, you might end up getting killed! Ever think of that?!” Takahisa scolded him harshly.

“Haruto’s taught me that already!”

“Guh...” There was that name again. Haruto, Haruto, Haruto. He’d made his way inside of everyone’s head while Takahisa wasn’t around. Even though that place should have been for him...

“Calm down, you two. I know I said we should discuss things, but I didn’t say we should argue,” Satsuki interrupted in the time that Takahisa fell silent.

“I... I just don’t want Masato to live a dangerous life. It’s safe in the castle, and as for learning swordcraft... If he absolutely had to, he could learn properly from the knights in the castle,” Takahisa said sullenly.

“Oh? Safety of the castle aside, Haruto’s an honorary knight himself, you know. He’s stronger than your average knight,” Satsuki noted.

“Exactly.” Masato nodded smugly.

“Masato, you have to try and understand how worried Takahisa is about you too, okay? Just imagining you running off somewhere and dying... anyone would feel uneasy,” Satsuki said to calm Masato, showing a smile with a bit of gloom to it. She had also been alone when she first came to this world, so perhaps that was why she could understand Takahisa’s feelings.

“Hmm... Well, yeah, I guess.” Masato nodded reluctantly.

“So, in conclusion... or rather, to summarize for now, Aki will be going to Centostella Kingdom with Takahisa, Miharu and Masato will stay with Haruto, and I’ll remain in the Galarc Kingdom—does that sound right?” Satsuki didn’t have any objection to the choices made as long as they were what the person in question decided for themselves, but it didn’t seem like Takahisa and Aki were as accepting. With that in mind, she looked at the two of them.

“...Are you okay with this, Aki? About leaving your ill feelings unaddressed and separating from Haruto like this,” Miharu asked her.

“...Who cares.” Aki averted her eyes from Miharu, giving an indifferent answer to hide her irritation.

“If you’re going to go with Takahisa, you should talk to him properly beforehand. Even if you’re going to move away from him, I hope you’d reconcile first.” Miharu placed a hand over her chest. At that, Aki ground her teeth and sneered in return.

“You’re completely on his side now, aren’t you? You’re not my ally anymore,” Aki replied sharply.

“...No. That’s wrong. I’ve always considered you special to me. You’re like my real little sister,” Miharu denied with great sadness.

“Then why aren’t you coming with us?! Don’t go with him—come with me and my brother! Stay with me!” Aki yelled at Miharu in grief.

“I... can’t do that. I’m sorry.” Miharu looked extremely distraught, but nevertheless expressed her intentions.

“I-Is it because you love him, Miharu? Is it because you love him that you can’t stay with me? You’d choose him instead?” Aki’s voice shook terribly as she spoke.

“It’s not like that...” Miharu gasped in shock. She wanted to stay with Haruto, not Aki. That may indeed have been the meaning of her choice, but the nuance was completely wrong.

“...Aki. It might not be my place to say this, since I’ve only heard of what happened through other people—but don’t you think that was too much?” Satsuki had been watching quietly as an outsider, but even she couldn’t let this conversation go on any longer.

“That’s right, Aki,” Masato also agreed indignantly.

“Love...” When Takahisa heard the possibility of Miharu being in love with Haruto, he fell speechless. That shock gradually shifted into panic.

“W-What does Haruto think?!” Takahisa asked loudly. Think about what? The implication of his question was too broad.

“...He says he’ll entrust the matter of who stays with who up to Miharu and the others themselves. He didn’t seem too enthusiastic about the thought of Miharu following him, though,” Satsuki replied.

“...That part is settled now. We talked it out, and I asked him. While he’s still reluctant about it, he accepted it.” Miharu looked at Satsuki and nodded.

“There you have it.” Satsuki smiled with a huff and looked at Takahisa. “Well done, Miharu. Though the fact that Haruto’s still reluctant is a little...” She sighed tiredly. Miharu simply smiled shyly.

“T-Then Haruto can just go with you...” Takahisa said in a great panic.

“...That’s not possible. Haruto has things he needs to do, too.” Recalling what Rio was trying to do, Satsuki’s face clouded over a bit.

“I-Is that the reason why he’s reluctant to bring Miharu along, perhaps?” When it came to the topic of Miharu, Takahisa had sharp instincts. His comment was right on the mark.

“Well, you could say that...” Satsuki nodded begrudgingly. Takahisa saw his chance in that and gulped before speaking.

“If Haruto doesn’t want you to follow him, wouldn’t forcing him to take you along just cause him trouble?”

“...You might be right. But I think that’s fine, too. He’s trying to live apart from a path of peace, so he needs someone beside him to pull him back into a regular life,” Satsuki said wearily, a knowing look on her face.

“He’s trying to live a turbulent life?” Unaware of the circumstances, Takahisa and the others cocked their heads dubiously.

“Hmm... Why doesn’t Haruto want Miharu to follow him in the first place? He’s fine with me going?” Masato asked Miharu and Satsuki, tilting his head.

“That’s... because...” Miharu couldn’t find the right words.

“Probably because Haruto was Amakawa Haruto in his past life, and Miharu was his childhood friend, I guess. I can’t speak for Haruto any more than that, though. Right, Miharu?” Satsuki gave an ambiguous but simple explanation to avoid going into detail, before seeking Miharu’s agreement in a kind voice.

“...Yes.” Miharu nodded quietly.

What’s... the deal with that... Takahisa was overwhelmingly flustered, but he grit his teeth to force that feeling down.

Even though I decided I would be the one to protect her... I would... Things had taken such an unexpected turn in the mere months they had been apart, he couldn’t accept that he would be separated from Miharu again.

Were they saying he was being kept out of the loop from the beginning? He didn’t want to feel the fear of losing someone important to him anymore, so he had decided he would tell Miharu his feelings.

Yet, before he could even tell Miharu his feelings, this happens...

I have to do something... something... Takahisa was grinding his teeth when Aki squeezed his hand. His expression changed with a gasp and he squeezed her hand back.

“It’ll be okay. I’ll be with you,” Aki whispered so that only Takahisa could hear, before speaking up. “All right, Miharu. I’ll do it. I’ll talk with Haruto.”

◇　◇　◇

Meanwhile, after Rio had left the drawing room and bid farewell to the others, he walked with Charlotte down a hallway of the castle.

“Where might we be headed?” Rio asked with a chuckle.

“The people from the main Beltrum government are leaving to return to their kingdom today, so we’ll be seeing them off first. After that, I have promised to have tea with Liselotte and was hoping you would be open to joining us,” Charlotte answered in a strangely cheerful mood.

“Is that so...” Rio didn’t know why she was in a good mood and watched her expression as he responded.

“Thank you very much, Sir Haruto,” Charlotte suddenly said.

“For what, may I ask?”

“For Aki and Masato. You brought them to the castle because you could trust us, no? That means Lady Satsuki has also decided to trust us to some extent. We’re very delighted about that. Perhaps you have already told her of our conversation during the dance at the banquet last night?”

“...Yes. However, I don’t believe my passing of the message had any influence on the outcome.” If Aki and Masato had desired it, they would have ended up coming to the castle anyway.

“You may claim that, but I don’t believe that to be the case. Father was also extremely delighted and praised you highly for it, Sir Haruto.” Charlotte smiled with a giggle. As they conversed, Rio and Charlotte walked towards the geometric garden that led to the castle gate.

Several horse carriages were waiting there as members of the Beltrum Kingdom royalty and nobility prepared to depart. They would be traveling to the Beltrum capital by enchanted ship, but the horse carriages were to take them from the castle to the harbor.

“It seems like they’ll be departing soon. Princess Christina and the hero are over there, too. I’m glad we made it in time. Now, come this way, Sir Haruto.” Rio followed Charlotte’s lead towards the nobility of the Beltrum Kingdom. Considering their past, he wouldn’t have approached them by choice, but the chance of his identity being discovered was extremely low. If anything, he wondered how many people from there actually remembered him.

“Are Princess Christina and Sir Rui available? I’d like to greet them and see them off. I’m the Galarc Kingdom’s second princess, Charlotte, and this is the honorary knight, Sir Amakawa,” Charlotte said to the knights guarding the horse carriages. It felt strange to have himself introduced as a knight, but it was certainly useful in how it made nobles more accommodating towards him.

“Please wait a moment.” A knight left in a fluster at the arrival of figures of such high status. Less than a minute later, Christina and Rui appeared with their guards in tow.

“Thank you for coming to see us off, Princess Charlotte, Sir Amakawa,” Christina greeted them gracefully.

“We probably won’t be seeing each other again for a while, so I wanted to at least bid you farewell. I had hoped we could talk more while you were here, but our positions make it difficult, after all. I’m happy we made it in time to see you off, though,” Charlotte said with a grin, glancing away from Christina nonchalantly. At the end of her gaze was Charles Arbor, who had accompanied the rest of the Beltrum Kingdom here.

Christina also shot Charles a glance before replying with a gentle smile. “We may be able to meet again sooner than expected, but you’re right. There’s always the possibility we won’t see each other again, so I’m glad we’re able to greet each other properly like this.” Then, she proceeded to direct her gaze at Rio. “Sir Amakawa, thank you for seeing us off, too. Sir Rui had also wanted to talk to you some more.”

“That’s... I’m honored.” Rio bowed his head deeply at Rui.

“I’m the one who is pleased to be able to see you again, Haruto. Like Princess Christina said, I wanted to speak with you,” Rui said, giving a refreshing smile.

“While it would be my pleasure, may I ask why?” Had he done something to attract his interest this much?

“It was because of what you said about your parents, I suppose. Your name sounds very similar to those of my hometown, so it made me feel a sense of familiarity, like you came from the same place as me. It seems that besides Satsuki, the other two heroes would rather be distanced from me, so if we ever have the chance to meet again, would you be willing to speak with me as a friend?” Rui said with a bittersweet smile, offering his hand to Rio for a handshake.

“Of course—I would be happy to.” Rio immediately shook Rui’s offered hand.

“Thank you.” Rui’s handsome face broke out in a happy smile. Then, Charles Arbor—who had been watching their exchange—approached.

“Are you two done? It’s almost time to depart,” he said to Christina and Rui.

“Yes. See you later, then,” Rui said and turned on his heel.

“Oh my, Sir Amakawa. You have some dust on your shoulder,” Christina suddenly pointed out.

“Oh, how embarrassing.” Rio reflexively moved his hand to pat away the dust.

“No, not over there...” Christina said, then took several steps towards Rio and whispered in Rio’s left ear so only he could hear.

“Thank you for saving Flora.”

Chapter 5: A Duel and the Result

The night of the duel with Satsuki, Rio informed her and Miharu that he would be stepping out for a moment. Then, he headed by himself to the guest rooms where Takahisa was staying with Aki, Masato, and Lilianna.

He didn’t bring Satsuki and Miharu along because he felt it was appropriate to speak to Takahisa and Aki alone.

Thus, he arrived before the rooms where Lilianna’s female knights stood guard. However, the two knights seemed more like young girls than adults. One was the petite Alice, who looked to be in her early- to mid-teens. The other was Kiara, who seemed similar to Rio’s age, in her mid-teens.

“Oh, it’s the really strong guy. Wow, he looks even cooler up close. Ah, my name’s Alice. The second daughter of a duke in the Centostella Kingdom.” The petite girl, Alice, introduced herself in an overly familiar way. She had a rather wild personality for a knight serving a member of the royal family.

“Hey, Alice!” Kiara immediately scolded her.

“F-Forgive me, Miss Kiara!” Alice apologized in a vacant voice.

“I’m not the one you should be apologizing to. Please forgive the rudeness, Sir Amakawa.” Kiara sighed tiredly, bowing her head at Rio.

“No, it doesn’t bother me. In fact, I should be the one apologizing for dropping by without warning, as I’d like to meet with Sir Takahisa. Could you pass on the message for me?”

“...Understood. Please wait a moment. You come too, Alice.” Kiara thought for a moment before entering the rooms with Alice, leaving Rio alone outside.

“Welcome. Please come inside.” Lilianna’s attendant, Frill, came out to invite Rio inside less than a minute later. Rio followed Frill into the room.

“Excuse me.” He bowed his head deeply as soon as he stepped in, his hand over his chest. Sitting on the high-class sofa inside the room was Takahisa, Aki, Masato and Lilianna.

“Welcome, Sir Haruto,” Lilianna greeted on behalf of the others.

“Thank you very much for agreeing to meet with me, despite the late hour.” Rio turned to Lilianna and bowed his head once more.

“I heard that you have business with Sir Takahisa.”

“Yes—Aki and Masato as well, to be precise. Princess Lilianna is welcome to sit in as well, if you so wish,” Rio said respectfully.

“...What is this about?” Takahisa asked Rio warily.

“The continuation of the conversation the six of us had today. After our match, Satsuki said some things to me. I have come here to inform you of my thoughts and opinions of the future.”

Rio’s answer made Lilianna close her eyes and think for a moment, before speaking up. “...In that case, please use the room over there.” She would probably hear the details from Takahisa later. Rio’s past life aside, Lilianna would have been informed about their plans for the future and who would be staying with whom.

“I am most grateful for your consideration.” Rio bowed deeply to express his gratitude.

“What are you waiting for? Let’s go.” Masato stood up first, prompting Takahisa and Aki to move as well.

“...Yeah. Let’s go, Takahisa.” Thus, the four of them moved to an adjacent bedroom. This was the bedroom where the three members of the Sendo family were staying. The room’s furnishings consisted of three beds, a desk, and four armchairs.

“Let’s sit down. I’ll sit beside Haruto.” Masato sat down on an armchair with a thump.

“Okay. Then, if you don’t mind.” Rio huffed with a smile and sat beside Masato. Takahisa and Aki took the seats opposite them. Once Rio confirmed that everyone was seated, he immediately began to speak.

“First, you should know that my thoughts are generally the same as what I told you during the match today. However, I no longer have the reluctance that I previously did. As long as everyone has thought about their answer, I have decided that I will respect that.”

“...What are you trying to say?” Takahisa asked with a dubious look.

“If Miharu and Masato say that they want to remain in my care as they have until now, then I will no longer try to stop them. As long as they have made that decision after hearing my thoughts, then they can do as they wish,” Rio said with a strangely discerning expression.

“...B-But you should! You should refuse them! Didn’t you say that you didn’t want them with you? You still think that way, don’t you?! So why have you changed your mind so suddenly? Refuse them more firmly! Stop stealing my family away from me!” Takahisa yelled in shock. Because Rio had openly indicated his intention to welcome Miharu and Masato, the negative feelings he had suppressed until now exploded.

“Takahisa...” Aki’s face fell as she watched the sudden change in her brother.

“I cannot,” Rio stated bluntly.

“...Why not?” Takahisa asked resentfully.

“Would my refusal change their minds? And if it did, would the two of them be happy to accept that? In the end, that wouldn’t be respecting their opinions. That’s why,” Rio answered smoothly. Masato smiled, looking somewhat happy about that.

“...Coward,” said Takahisa. “You’re a coward. Even though you say you don’t want Miharu with you, you don’t want to refuse her either—that’s cowardice! How does doing something like that equal respect?”

“You have a point. I thought the same. However, if it doesn’t count as respect whether I refuse them or not, then I at least want to show my acceptance. It’d be better than completely running away by refusing to accept them—that’s what Satsuki told me. So I decided I’d face them properly.” Rio explained his thoughts in a calm voice.

“But that’s—!” That’s just convenient for you, was what Takahisa was about to respond with.

“...Then are you running away from me, Haruto? If you let me go to Centostella Kingdom like this, wouldn’t that be the same as avoiding the problem with me?” Aki added to the conversation in an aggressive tone.

“I have no intention of doing that. That’s why I came here alone. I wanted to face you without Miharu and Satsuki present. If you allow it, I’d like to talk to you properly, one-on-one.” Rio didn’t falter as he answered Aki.

“...” Aki was rendered speechless for a moment.

“Aki!” Takahisa reflexively called the name of his stepsister, looking at her pleadingly. Was this man about to steal Aki from him as well? He couldn’t allow that.

“...Because Miharu and I knew Amakawa Haruto, we unconsciously see you as Amakawa Haruto instead and overlap their existences. That’s what you said, right?”

“Yes, I did say that.”

“Do you dislike being overlapped with him?”

“That’s... not quite right. What I don’t want is to be overlapped with a different person and compared to him.” And consequently, disappointing their expectations. Making them regret staying with him. That’s why he wanted to reveal himself and keep his distance before such a thing could happen. Even now, he still had the desire to stay away from them.

“I can only see that ‘different person’ reasoning as nothing more than a convenient excuse to run away.” Aki glared at Rio with a look of contempt.

“It’s true that we’re different people. I do things that Amakawa Haruto would never do. Deeds that Amakawa Haruto would feel greatly opposed to committing, I would do without batting an eye.”

“...What, for example?” Aki asked doubtfully.

“Killing people.” Rio indifferently stated what a Japanese person would feel the most disgust towards committing.

“...” Aki was at a loss for words. Takahisa had also fallen speechless, out of shock. Only Masato was less surprised than the two of them, though his eyes did widen faintly.

“When it comes to a battle, I will kill. If I can only protect myself by killing, if a battle can only be ended through killing, then I have no choice but to do so. I’ve come to accept that. Even at this very moment, there’s someone out there that I must kill.” Knowing the morals of Japanese people was precisely why Rio considered himself incompatible with Miharu and the others. In general, he thought of Japanese morals as precious things to keep, and while he was greatly influenced by the values of Amakawa Haruto during times of peace, he considered those values to be a lie deep down inside, where he was cruel and repulsive.

“Have you ever killed someone before?” Takahisa asked with a look of complete contempt.

“I have,” Rio said without any shame. He felt it was better to answer directly.

“So you’re a murderer...” Takahisa muttered with spite.

“Indeed I am.”

“...Killing just because it’s necessary doesn’t make it right. It’s unacceptable on a human level. I can’t leave Miharu or Masato in the care of a person like you,” Takahisa said with a cold calmness, having found an excuse to justify himself.

“Hey, bro!” Masato tried to intervene.

“Shut up! As if I could leave my precious brother in the hands of a murderer!” Takahisa yelled over him.

“...You’re going too far,” Masato muttered, his shoulders trembling with rage.

“Miharu won’t be happy being with you. It’d be better for her sake to be with me, the hero. I would be able to protect Miharu,” Takahisa claimed, as though convincing himself he was the better one between them.

“Huh? As if you’d be able to beat Haruto, bro,” Masato sneered.

“H-Haruto, you also felt the same way when you told Miharu she was better off away from you, no?”

“...Indeed.” Rio nodded once.

“Then... You’re a coward! If you know that much, you’re a coward for refusing to reject Miharu! Miharu only wants to follow you because she doesn’t know you’re a murderer. Probably because she sees you as a different person, like you said. She’d definitely feel disgusted if she knew,” Takahisa said fiercely.

“...She is aware.”

“What?” Rio’s quiet statement made Takahisa lose all his fervor.

“Miharu knows I have killed people. I’ve told both Miharu and Satsuki everything.”

“Wha...” And she wanted to be with him despite that?! Miharu would choose someone so selfish? Not to mention Satsuki, who was an upperclassman he had always respected...

“Is she a fool? Miharu...” Aki muttered bitterly in disbelief. However, this meant there were no more means of stopping Miharu as they had wanted to.

“Do you really, truly intend on accepting Miharu like this? Even though you know Miharu may come to regret everything. No, she’ll definitely regret everything!” Takahisa seemed to have the same thought as Aki, as he objected in a panicked state.

“If she wants to come along in spite of that, then I will no longer refuse her. Although, I don’t know if I’ll be able to respond to her as Amakawa Haruto...” While Rio looked a little guilty at that, he stated his opinion clearly.

“...I won’t stand for this,” Takahisa murmured, then raised his voice. “I absolutely won’t stand for this. As if I could leave Miharu in your hands!” His heart was already backed into a corner, making him act on pure desperation, but he couldn’t afford to back down here.

“...Then, what would you like to do?” Rio knew things would come to this. He had come here prepared for it.

“Duel with me. If I win, you must reject Miharu’s wishes. I’m going to win and prove your dishonesty. Watch me!” Of all things, Takahisa challenged Rio to a fight. No matter what the pretense for it, it was a request to fight him.

“...Your actions seem to be an attempt to bend Miharu’s will to suit your own desires, in my eyes,” Rio pointed out.

“A-Are you trying to justify yourself?!” Takahisa yelled back, guilt laden in his voice.

“No, nothing of the sort. If you wish to have a duel in order to treat Miharu like some kind of object, then I definitely will not lose. At the very least, I won’t attempt to bend Miharu to my own will. That’s all.” Rio gave his stance indifferently.

“...Sorry, but I’ll be supporting Haruto,” Masato suddenly said.

“What?!” Takahisa glared at Masato with a frown.

“I’m willing to bet on it, too. If Haruto loses to you, I’ll do whatever you tell me to do. How about it?” Masato glared back in a challenge.

“S-Stop it, you two...” Aki watched the relationship between her two brothers break down helplessly.

Masato frowned as he looked at Aki, before he stood up brusquely. “...Let’s go, Haruto. It’s already late, so you should just settle the match first thing tomorrow. Sorry, but could you let me stay in your room? I can’t deal with sleeping here anymore.” He wanted to leave the room now.

“...” Takahisa seemed to accept Masato’s challenge, as he didn’t bother to stop him. He furrowed his brows as he sat silently. There was nothing more to say here.

“...All right. Let’s go.” Rio sighed and stood up. He proceeded to guide Masato out of the room with a hand on his back.

“...” Aki looked like she wanted to say something to Rio’s departing figure, but her mouth didn’t move. Thus, Rio and Masato left the bedroom and came face-to-face with Lilianna in the living room, seated on the sofa with a frustrated expression.

“Please accept my deepest apologies for causing a stir so late at night.” Rio bowed deeply to Lilianna. Even if she hadn’t heard every word of the conversation, she must have been able to overhear the yelling from the bedroom.

“Not at all...” Lilianna shook her head slowly.

“Also, I know this is extremely selfish of me, but Sir Takahisa and I have decided to have a match tomorrow morning, just like with Lady Satsuki. Of course, I will forfeit if Princess Lilianna has any objections, but may I have your approval?” Rio requested politely, hanging his head.

“As long as it is Sir Takahisa’s will, I will not stop anyone. If possible, I would also like to entrust Masato to Sir Amakawa’s care tonight, though it may be inconvenient for you. In regards to the match, I shall arrange everything with His Majesty for approval.” Lilianna dropped her gaze slightly, her beautiful face clouding over fleetingly.

“...I am most grateful for that. Then, if you would excuse me.” Rio placed his right hand over his chest and bowed his head once more, before returning to Satsuki’s quarters with Masato.

The next morning, in the arena that was adjacent to the castle and away from the parade grounds, Rio faced Takahisa. It wasn’t only the venue that differed from his match with Satsuki yesterday—to prevent this match from becoming a spectacle, the audience seats were filled with only a select few people who were involved.

Among them were, of course, Miharu, Satsuki, Masato, and Aki, as well as Lilianna and Charlotte.

However, Aki wasn’t seated together with Miharu, Satsuki, and Masato; instead, she was seated beside Lilianna a short distance away. Her eyes were fixed on Takahisa.

Meanwhile, Miharu and Satsuki had been brought to the arena after being informed that the discussion resulted in a duel.

“Hey, Masato. How did things end up like this?” Miharu asked him—Masato was seated beside her.

“’Cause my brother’s an idiot. Well, just think of it like a fight between men. You can ask Haruto yourself after the match is over.” Last night, Masato had returned to their rooms with Rio and immediately gone to sleep in a huff. He acted like this every time Miharu asked him for the details. She knew that Rio went to have a discussion with the Sendo family and could tell that some kind of argument had resulted from it, but Rio awkwardly avoided giving her any details, leaving Miharu at a loss.

“Haruto’s probably trying to communicate with us in his own way, don’t you think? There are things we won’t know without clashing, and I’m sure he’ll do the same to you one day, Miharu. So let’s just believe in him and just watch over the match for now.” Satsuki didn’t know about the details of Rio and Takahisa’s argument either, but her mouth was curved into a gentle smile. She had kept what she had discussed with Rio after their match yesterday a secret, but Miharu had a feeling that their conversation played a part in this.

“...Okay.” Miharu nodded with a sigh.

“Well, at least there’s no need to worry about the result of the match. I can’t imagine Haruto would ever lose, after all. If you still think you can win after watching Satsuki’s battle yesterday, then you’re too naive, bro!” Masato said, huffing through his nose.

“Seems like they’re about to begin.” Satsuki seemed to agree with Masato’s statement as her lips quirked in a smile, before she turned her attention to the field. The referee had just started to explain the rules for the match.

“The only permitted weapons are training swords. Victory will be decided purely on sword technique. The hero, Sir Takahisa, is permitted to use divine arms to enhance his body, and Sir Amakawa is permitted to do the same with his enchanted sword. The match will be decided by either stopping on the verge of a decisive blow or landing a telling blow on an area other than the face. Please restrain your attacks to a nonlethal degree. Being disarmed alone will not count as defeat. Are these rules agreeable?” A young knight named Kyle was acting as the referee. He looked at Rio and Takahisa in confirmation of the rules.

“Yes!” Takahisa nodded eagerly while Rio inclined his head in a relaxed manner.

“Understood.”

“Both sides, distance yourselves and ready your weapons,” the referee said, raising his hand in the air. Then, once the two of them had enough distance between them, he confirmed that they were holding their weapons at the ready.

“Begin!” he yelled, swinging his hand down to signal the start of the match.

“Hah!” Takahisa yelled angrily as he approached Rio. The physical enhancement of a divine arm was powerful and his speed easily surpassed human limits. Though not by much, his movements did show signs he had been training with a sword. However, from Rio’s point of view, he was full of openings.

I could end the match in an instant, but... In order to whittle down the stubborn Takahisa’s hostility a little, defeating him easily wouldn’t be enough. He had to make him surrender after pushing Takahisa to give him everything he had. With that decided, Rio took on his opponent’s ferocious attack head-on.

“Raaaagh!” Takahisa launched a countless number of sword attacks at Rio. Rio moved after every one, swinging his sword to divert the course of every attack made his way. Roughly ten seconds passed in this way.

“Kuh...” Takahisa felt like his attacks were having no effect at all—he didn’t even feel like he was swinging his sword at Rio anymore. He made eye contact with Rio’s all-seeing gaze and involuntarily retreated to put distance between them. However, Rio remained still. He stood there, waiting for Takahisa to make the next move; in part to restrain himself and not inadvertently defeat him.

“Do you plan on standing there the whole time?!” What arrogance! Takahisa made full use of his vastly-improved physical abilities to throw Rio off balance. Even then, Rio did not move to attack him. Takahisa ran in circles around Rio before launching an attack from behind, seeing that Rio was the most open there. “Gwah?!” It was as though Rio had eyes on the back of his head. Without even sparing a glance, he turned around and swung his sword, immediately knocking away the sword Takahisa was swinging. The recoil made Takahisa stumble backwards. When he made eye contact with Rio’s cold gaze, he grimaced in humiliation.

What was that look in his eyes?! Is he looking down on me when he’s a murderer himself?! All while preaching about how he’s trying to respect Miharu’s opinion, this hypocrite! I won’t... I won’t let a murderer look down on me! How could I leave Miharu by the side of a murderer?! Not my... my Miharu...! He didn’t want Miharu stolen away from him. With that single thought in mind, Takahisa was overcome with an almost overwhelming sense of paranoia as he moved.

He wanted to win. To fight—and win. Against this man... This hypocrite! He had to win to prove to Miharu that he was stronger than Rio. However, that was an impossible feat, to a degree that he was unaware of. To him, as long as he won, as long as he emerged victorious, Miharu would understand. Takahisa believed that beyond a doubt. No, that belief was the only thing that kept him going. However—

“Dammit, at this rate...!”

He couldn’t win. Takahisa had the faint hunch that was the case.

But he didn’t want to lose. He couldn’t lose. That was how much resolution he had coming into this battle, putting his pride and his life on the line.

“Haaaah!” Takahisa heightened the ability of his divine arms enhancement and charged directly at Rio. He moved at the speed of a flying arrow, shooting straight for Rio.

However, Takahisa’s passion had caused him to make a mistake. Both he and Rio had increased the strength of their physical bodies so that a hit from a training sword would hurt, but wouldn’t be life-threatening. But Takahisa’s current speed was creating enough kinetic energy to ignore the increased body strength, packing enough of a punch to deal a fatal wound.

With this speed, I can do it! Takahisa was certain of his victory and rejoiced. Without any hesitation at all, he poured every ounce of strength he had into the sword clutched between both his hands and swung it at Rio.

“Wha...?!” His swinging sword cut through the air, leaving Takahisa speechless. There had been no resistance at all. There wasn’t even a trace of Rio left before him. Why?! Takahisa felt a sense of doubt that was closing in on anger, when—

“Guh!” Takahisa felt a light impact on his back, and in the next moment, he toppled off-balance. He had been thrust away by Rio, but the attack had clearly been held back. It wasn’t enough to be considered a telling hit. The referee hadn’t spoken up, either.

“What?!” Takahisa frantically scrambled to turn around with his sword at the ready, yelling in the direction of the contact. However, Rio was nowhere to be seen.

“Your field of view is too narrow,” Rio’s calm voice echoed through Takahisa’s back.

“Wah!” Takahisa swung his sword in a panic.

“In a battle where you’ve already become hot-headed, hastening your speed past the point of control will only make you lose sight of your target. That’s why your field of view is narrowing. The same can be said of you and Miharu...” Rio leaped backwards in a relaxed manner, avoiding Takahisa’s attack as he spoke.

“...Is that sarcasm? You have no right to be saying that!” Takahisa spat hatefully.

“Perhaps,” Rio agreed easily. To Takahisa, it felt like Rio was infuriatingly showing off the difference in their capabilities through his relaxed attitude. He charged at Rio vigorously.

“You’re not worthy of Miharu!”

“I know.”

“You murderous hypocrite!”

“I know that too.”

“I absolutely won’t allow it!”

“Do I need your permission?” That was true arrogance.

“That’s why I’m going to win this match!” Takahisa declared, swinging his sword at Rio. The drawn sword drew a sharp arc downwards towards his opponent.

“Wha?!” Of all the things to do, Rio released his sword. He stabbed the tip into the ground, letting it stand vertically. However, there was no stopping Takahisa’s blade any longer.

It was at this point that Takahisa finally feared that he might end up killing Rio. Suddenly, Rio stepped forward of his own accord.

But it wasn’t as though Rio intended on dying, either. Aiming for the moment when Takahisa’s fervor weakened slightly, he caught the blade of the sword between his hands.

Epilogue: Rebirth of Childhood Friends

Rio had his left arm wrapped around Miharu as he used his right hand to skillfully control his sword, making a gentle return to the Galarc royal castle.

“...I wonder what will happen after this,” Rio asked Miharu with a half-resigned expression as they approached the castle. How could they explain the circumstances to the people of the Galarc and Centostella kingdoms?

“Yeah... I wonder what’ll happen.” It felt like the situation would grow completely out of hand. Miharu imagined it with a stiff smile.

“Perhaps it was excessive of me to punch Takahisa.” Despite his words, Rio had a slight smile on his face.

“I think that was fine. Violence is necessary sometimes...” Violence didn’t seem to be her strong point, as Miharu was nodding as though to convince herself.

“I’ll make sure you’ll never be in a situation where you need to act violent, so don’t worry,” Rio immediately interjected.

“But I think I’d like to defend myself, at least. I want to learn properly. From Haru-kun... Ah, umm. From Haruto.” Miharu requested timidly, watching for Rio’s reaction.

“...I don’t mind,” Rio suddenly said.

“Huh?” Miharu gasped.

“I don’t mind if you call me Haru-kun sometimes. I’m sure there’ll be times where you want to reminisce about the past.” Rio’s voice was a little bashful as he spoke.

“Is that because you see me as your childhood friend?” And did that mean he would face Miharu as Amakawa Haruto? Miharu lifted her face right up to Rio’s.

“Ahaha.” Rio laughed, trying to brush off Miharu’s question. Come to think of it, the Miharu that Amakawa Haruto knew always brought her face close like this when she asked questions, even without her knowing of it.

“I think the way that you try to laugh off questions is a bad habit of yours, Haru-kun,” Miharu pouted a little.

Rio looked up at the sky before returning Miharu’s close-distance gaze. “I can at least promise to do my best to meet your demands, seeing as you say you want to be together in the future as well. Will that do for you?”

“...Y-Yes. We can start there...” When Miharu made eye contact with him up close, she ducked her head out of embarrassment. Such actions were exactly reminiscent of the girl that Amakawa Haruto knew.

Your feelings reached Haruto properly. It was worth transmitting your conversation with Takahisa, Aishia’s voice echoed.

“My... conversation with Takahisa...?” Miharu cocked her head in suspicion for a moment. “Y-You were listening?! You heard my conversation with Takahisa?!” She remembered what she had said to Takahisa and turned bright red.

“Ahaha.” Rio once again laughed to gloss over the situation. Miharu once again unconsciously drew her face near Rio’s.

“Answer me!”

“Speaking of which, weren’t you discussing things with Aishia before I ever named myself with the Amakawa family name?” Rio suddenly remembered.

“Huh?! T-That’s not... true...” Miharu’s eyes were clearly wavering.

“Well, I’ll ask Aishia for details later. We’ll consider it even with that.”

“It’s totally not even at all!” I basically confessed to him! No, but I didn’t say it in front of him, so maybe it doesn’t count? Miharu tried to persuade herself as her face flushed red.

“Then forgive me, Mii-chan.” Rio gave a shy smile before uttering Miharu’s nickname teasingly.